skinbase.org 2004-06-04

# Skinbase.org / Privacy Policy

**SkinBase Submissions Policy**  
SkinBase reserves the right to prohibit any submission that it deems offensive. Some of the items that can be seen as offensive include any pornographic, racial or hate-based works. By submitting your work to SkinBase, you also agree that you are the legal copyright holder to all said submitted works (or parts-thereof) or that you have permission from the original work's artist. If a submitted piece of artwork is found to not be that of the submitting artist, he/she shall be responsible for any legal action that may arise due to copyright infringement. We do not claim ownership of the artwork submitted to SkinBase as all artwork submitted is the copyrighted work of its original artist. The files submitted by the users of SkinBase are not checked for viruses and it is recommended that all users check their downloaded files with a virus checker. SkinBase takes no responsibility for anything contained in a downloaded file as the contents of each file are not checked by the SkinBase website or it's admins.

**SkinBase User Policy**  
As SkinBase is a general-age website, we ask that all registered users behave in an appropriate manner at all times. As stated in the above Submissions Policy, we do not allow the use of offensive material. Do not post material that is pornographic, racial or hate-based. SkinBase reserves the right to cancel a member's account along with all files submitted by that member at any given time without warning. SkinBase also allows its users to remove their submitted artwork at any given time. If a submitted piece of work is found to be not that of it's submitting artist (aka - a rip), then action will be taken to have that piece removed. Repeat offenders will have their accounts cancelled. If you'd like to notify SkinBase of such a submission, please feel free to contact a site admin.

**SkinBase Privacy Policy**  
Information is collected at several points from users of the SkinBase site. SkinBase is the sole owner of this information and will not sell or disclose it to any third party. Information is gathered in the following situations:

**Membership Signup**  
To fully use the SkinBase website, a user must first apply for membership. Information requested at the time of registration (for example - name and email address) is used to create the user's statistics page (member details page). The details provided are accessible by other members visiting the SkinBase website, except email address which **WILL NOT** appear anywhere at Skinbase.org. These details are also used to contact the user (via form) about items specific to the SkinBase website. A member will only receive these emails if the user has chosen to receive emails from SkinBase by applying to join the SkinBase mailing list. Members may opt to remove themselves from the mailing list at any given time. It should be noted that by making your details public in this way, that you do allow yourself to receive unsolicited email/s from other parties.

**Cookies**  
SkinBase uses cookies to help make each user's visit easier and more interactive. By storing a cookie, the user does not have to log in to the site each time he/she visits the site and the user also gets to use features such as the messageboard and online chat. Cookies are in no way linked to the personal information disclosed at signup.

**Outside Advertising**  
SkinBase uses outside advertising on its website. These advertising companies may also place cookies on your hard drive to collect information (not including name, email address and phone number) in regards to your visit to this and other sites in order to try and bring you advertising in relation to your interests.

**IP Logging**  
SkinBase also logs IP addresses to help administer the website and track user's actions on the website. These details do not contain any personally identifiable information.

**Sharing of Information**  
SkinBase will only share information with third parties if required to do so by law, or if by doing so we can protect the SkinBase website and/or it's users. If you do not wish for others to know your personal details (for example - name and email address), it is recommended that you do not apply for membership.

**Links**  
SkinBase links to several other websites. SkinBase does not control the content of any outside websites and can not be held accountable for their content. We also are not in control of the privacy policies of these sites and recommend that all members carefully read the privacy policies of other websites that collect personally identifiable information.

**Messageboard Posts and Polls**  
At any given time, users have the ability to participate in the online polls or messageboards. Use of these facilities is voluntary. Poll information is in no way linked to the personal information disclosed at signup. Any information given on the messageboard becomes public information and users should therefore exercise caution before disclosing private information.

**Children under the Age of 13**  
As SkinBase is a general-audience website, we can not allow children under the age of 13 to sign up for membership (in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act). We ask that parents instead sign up for membership and monitor their children's activity on the website. 

**Editing Your Profile or Submissions**  
If a user's personally identifiable information changes, we will always attempt to find a way to allow the user to update these details. You can make these changes by using the 'edit profile' page or by contacting a site admin.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**  
If we make changes to this policy, we will let members know by posting mention of the changes on the homepage of the SkinBase website. If we decide to use the personal details collected at membership signup (or during any other stage of a user's onsite activity) in any manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will let the user know via email. Users will be given a choice as to whether they want their information used in a different manner.

**Contact SkinBase**  
If you have questions not answered in this policy in regards to the daily running of this site, please feel free to email at [info@skinbase.org](mailto:info@skinbase.org)
